wishdates.com 2014-12-22

# Wishdates - Privacy Default

Privacy is a very important part of Wishdates activities. We take a responsible approach to User’s data, which is why we have developed a policy that guarantees their full protection. 

Use of Wishdates services means that you have read and agreed to the Privacy Policy. 

##  About Wishdates and your information on the site 

Wishdates is a community using revolutionary way to find interesting people for communication and close acquaintances. We get different kinds of information from users of our service. To complete our online registration form you have to provide us with information about you, such as your name, your e-mail address, your gender, your date of birth, your location details and other data. These details are available to you by accessing ‘My Profile’ page, which gives you the chance to correct or update your information at any time. 

The information which relates to your name, sex, age, location, and the information which you see fit to share in your profile will be publicly available to other users. For example, you can specify your ethnicity, education, religion, marital status, interests, etc., and place pictures. If you post personal information, it means that you agree with this Privacy Policy. You can also restrict other users from accessing your data. 

We can also keep a record of any correspondence you send us, as well as information that other users or third parties send about your activities or materials published on the website. This information is collected in files and is available to authorized personnel. We also may collect other people’s comments, which were sent to the complaints section. 

##  Information Collected Automatically 

To save a usage session, we use a cookie — this is the information sent by a web server to a user’s computer to store in a browser. Session cookies are deleted when you close your browser. If you still want to stop saving a cookie in the future, please check the instructions in the ‘Help’ menu in your browser. 

While using our Web site or application, we automatically store information about your e-mail and IP-addresses. All web sites collect this information for analytical purposes. However, the User assumes all responsibility for protecting their own confidentiality, in the case of disclosure of personal information by the User himself, for example, by using messages. We reserve the right to restrict rights to the accounts of users who use the site in violation of our [Terms of Use](http://www.wishdates.com/en/terms). 

We use third-party advertising companies in order to display advertisements on the Web site. These companies may use non-personal information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other websites. Advertising companies such as third-party vendors, use cookies to serve ads on our site. Using cookies allows them to show site users most relevant ads about goods and services. Most web browsers allow you to delete cookies from your computer’s hard drive if necessary, to block or reject all cookies, or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your internet browser’s instructions or help menu to learn more about these functions. 

The Website Administration has a partnership with Google which places, on a reimbursable basis, promotional materials and advertisements on the site (including but not limited to, text, hyperlinks). In the framework of this cooperation, Site Administration informs all interested parties the following information: 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site; 
  * The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites displaying AdSense for content ads; 
  * The use of DART cookie files by Google, allows it to collect and use information about the Site visitors (except your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number), about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services; 
  * Google is guided by its own privacy policy during the collection of this information; 
  * Site Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy Google](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

##  How Do We Use Your Information? 

We may use the information site users provide Wishdates with, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts for improving our website or online service. User data might not also be taken into account when processing payments and conducting transactions. We may also use the information to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems in accordance with our [Terms of Use](http://www.wishdates.com/en/terms). We can send you notifications of new messages or other functions of the site. You can withdraw these notifications at any time by changing the [settings](http://www.wishdates.com/en/settings/settings) on your User Account. 

Using the service, you accept the fact that your profile information and other materials published by you, including information addressing your feelings and dignity, may be available in other countries. Please note that countries outside Europe may have lower standards of data protection. Please remember that we may also use the published material in the open access of Wishdates network for advertising and promotional purposes on our partner sites. 

##  Disclosure of Information 

Information that identifies you, such as your password, isn’t available to anyone except you. Wishdates does not provide personal information about its users to third parties, except in cases provided by law. In order to ensure intellectual property rights and other rights Wishdates cooperates with law enforcement authorities and other organizations. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to ensure safety or to protect our rights. 

##  Using someone else’s information 

Users can not use someone else’s information for commercial purposes, make illegal actions or to engage in spam. Accounts view using the programs and scripts is banned. It is forbidden to try to open or uncover other people’s accounts or otherwise violate the privacy of Wishdates users, or to create obstacles to them in using the Site. We reserve the right to block access to people who abuse the information of other users, or otherwise violate the [Terms of Use](http://www.wishdates.com/en/terms). 

##  Safety of the password 

We ensure the confidentiality of your password for our part. However, if you make a disclosure of your password to any third parties, then your account and your information may be used and you will be responsible for the actions taken with your profile. If you have lost control over the confidentiality of your password for some reason, you need to change your password. You can do this in the [‘Settings’](http://www.wishdates.com/en/settings/settings) section. 

##  View and Update Personal Information 

All of your personal information on our site is available to you, you can change it when you see fit. You can change your e-mail, password, photographs and personal information in your profile. Be sure to refresh the data, if someone used your personal profile on Wishdates. We suggest you periodically change your password to ensure a high level of protection and to reduce the risk of anyone hacking your account. 

##  Security Measures 

Wishdates provides the necessary measures to ensure the safety and security of your information, and to prevent its improper use. Keep in mind however that there is no absolute security on the web, but our technicians do take care of you and constantly work on the safety of your data. 

##  Deleting your profile 

Wishdates users may choose to delete all information about themselves and their own profile. You must enter the site using your login and password and select the appropriate options in the [‘Settings’](http://www.wishdates.com/en/settings/settings) section. 

##  Inviting Your Friends 

Wishdates gives all users the opportunity to invite friends to the site. You can invite friends and acquaintances through social networks and e-mail services. In the second case, we ask the person you want to invite for an e-mail address, and then send him / her a message asking to join us. Wishdates keeps this address in order to automatically connect a guest and a friend who sent the invitation. We don’t sell these e-mail addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. By providing us with information about your friends, you confirm you have their permission to do so. 

##  Exporting your contacts 

If the user decides to export their contacts, he / she confirms that the invitation by e-mail or through the social network will be sent on his / her behalf to the contacts that were exported. Wishdates stores the names and e-mail-addresses of contacts in order to automatically connect them in future to those who sent the invitation. We don’t sell these e-mail addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. By providing us with information about your friends, you confirm you have their permission to do so. 

##  Privacy Policy Changes 

If we decide to change our Privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page, this Privacy policy page and other appropriate places. That way you will be notified how we collect and use information and under what circumstances disclosure is possible. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. So please view this page occasionally. In case of significant changes you will be notified by e-mail or it will be published on the home page.
